## Oleksandr Buhai

368-299-7666 | oleksandr.buugay@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-buhai-95a35227b https://github.com/OleksandrBuhai

## SUMMARY

Experienced front end developer with a professional background in crafting complex, interactive web projects since 2021. High at cross-browser development, web standards, usability, responsive web development, and application architecture. I enjoy creating products that will benefit people in the future.

## EDUCATION

IT-Incubator.io

May 2020 - May 2021 Front-End Developer

NTUU KPI

Aug. 2015 - May 2019 Studied Manufacturing Engineering

Kyiv, Ukraine

**IPTKisSUMDU** 

Konotop, Ukraine College Degree in Manufacturing Technology May 2013 - May 2015

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer Apr 2023 - Jul 2023

Berlin Labs LLC Remote

• Developing new user-facing features using React

• Participation in the development of a project for the sale of photo \ video.

• Optimizing components for maximum performance

• Building reusable components

Jun 2022 - Mar 2023 Front-End Developer

 $Self\ employ$ Mladá Boleslav, CZ • Development of landing pages;

• Developing features to enhance the user experience

• Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.

• Ensuring web design is optimized for smartphones

• Fix Bugs

**Production Supervisor** May 2019 - Dec 2021 Škoda Auto Mladá Boleslav, CZ

• Addressing technical challenges

Managed both equipment and a team, ensuring smooth operations and quality standards

Dec 2016 – Jul 2017 Graphic Assistant Kyiv, Ukraine

Mindy Support

 Data Processing for Neural Networks • Image Processing for Future Use

Projects

 $Portfolio \mid React, JavaScript, CSS$ 

• https://oleksandrbuhai.github.io/Portfolio/

• Working with libraries framer-motion , React styled component, tsparticles

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Lanuages: English, Czech, Ukranian

ProgLanguages: JavaScript, TypeScript HTML/CSS

Frameworks: React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind CSS, jQuery, Material-UI

Developer Tools: Git, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ